Storm Doris: Woman killed by debris in Wolverhampton named
Privacy is Power
Bill Gates: Pathogen could kill 30m in a year
Duffy: 'There's a difference' on white terror and Muslim terror
"13,000 people hanged in secret at Syrian prison, Amnesty says"
Analysis: Does the settlements law have a prayer of getting past the High Court?
Why many Indian politicians have a criminal record
White House Says Bathrobe Anecdote Is All Wet
I Was on the National Security Council. Bannon Doesn’t Belong There.
EU faces crisis as IMF warns Greek debts are on ‘explosive’ path
Britain's housing crisis is at its worst for 20 years – yet obvious answers are ignored
Biotech Executives Sign Letter Against Immigration Order
ACLU Asks Judge to Order Return of  Those Removed Under Travel Ban
'Day Without Immigrants': Protest closes restaurants in US
Oliver Dearlove: Trevor Timon jailed for one-punch killing
"GOP leaders unveil new health law outline, divisions remain"
Man pleads guilty to buying rifles in San Bernardino attack
Samsung heir Lee Jae-yong arrested in South Korea
Baby taken from family amid concern over formula milk comment
Pakistan: IS attack on Sufi shrine in Sindh kills dozens
Alphabet Scraps Plan to Blanket Globe With Internet Balloons
McConnell intends to replace 'Obamacare' without Democrats
"AP Exclusive: If California dam failed, people likely stuck"
Immigrant haven of Miami-Dade votes against sanctuary status
Marmite owner Unilever sees no merit in Kraft takeover
"RBS plans: Williams & Glyn sale should be dropped, UK says"
Bin lorry crash driver Harry Clarke admits reckless driving charge
Kim Jong-nam death suspect 'thought she was in TV prank'
McCain: Dictators 'get started by suppressing free press'
DeVos given U.S. Marshals Service protection
Mosul assault: Iraq troops make headway against IS
On Mosul front line with BBC's Quentin Sommerville
Probe into Randox Manchester 'manipulated' drug tests data
Bogota explosion: Many injured in blast near bullring
Brexit: Mandelson urges Lords not to 'throw in towel'
Kraft Pulls $143 Billion Unilever Bid After Early Opposition
US Aircraft Carrier Begins Patrol in South China Sea
Suicide Bombing at Market in Somalian Capital Kills Dozens
"Blast near Bogota bullring injures 31, reports say"
"Reflecting on one very, very strange year at Uber"
"As Obesity Rises, Remote Pacific Islands Plan to Abandon Junk Food"
Thousands of demonstrators across US say 'Not My President'
Iraqi troops advance on western Mosul as Mattis holds talks
"AP, other media ask judge to order release of iPhone records"
"Respect Brexit decision, peers urged"
FA reforms: Chairman Greg Clarke to quit if government does not back plans
Swindon dig: Police search at Christopher Halliwell's former home
Islamic State battle: View from Iraq's front line
Staffordshire mother says breastfed son ‘spotted cancer’
Steve Hewlett: Radio 4 presenter dies at the age of 58
Judges hammer attorneys on both sides of travel ban case
DeVos ekes out confirmation win as Pence casts historic vote
Police face complaints about 'third-shift terror squad'
Israeli allies condemn settlement law as lawsuits loom
First lady says high profile could mean millions for brand
Social care fund 'fails to reduce pressure on hospital beds'
Brexit rebellion avoided after 'meaningful vote' offer
Louisiana tornadoes: 'The whole house fell apart'
Nigel Farage 'frightened' to go outside as UKIP is 'demonised'
Border agents ask Muhammad Ali's son: 'Are you Muslim?'
Labour leadership: Watson says not the time for a contest
"One dead, two injured in Heidelberg car attack"
Woman charged after Dexter Neal dog death
How do you move an oil platform from China to the UK?
Mosul battle: Kurdish reporter Shifa Gardi killed in Iraq
Hans Rosling: Data visionary and educator dies aged 68
Dakota Access Pipeline to win US Army permit for completion
Apple Hires Amazon’s Fire TV Head to Run Apple TV Business
Energy Transfer to Get Dakota Access Pipeline Approval From U.S.
Travel ban hearing: Fiery judges put lawyers on their heels
Law is on DOJ's side in court showdown
"It's a Muslim ban, and it's unconstitutional"
"Inheritance tax trap: more than 100,000 families won't get the new tax break"
Thousands of children and teenagers with anorexia forced to wait months for help
French farmers hope Marine Le Pen will free them from EU 'straitjacket'
Revealed: Labour’s secret 'script' orders MPs to say winning Copeland was an ‘uphill task’
Police shoot man who 'drove into people' in German city of Heidelberg leaving one dead and two injured
That’s the Way the Party Crumbles
Warren cut off during Sessions debate after criticism
Cruz: ACA opponents map looks like election map - CNN Video
Jake Tapper spars with Kellyanne Conway over WH falsehoods
"Cruz, Sanders face off on Obamacare"
Islamic State Drones Terrorize Iraqi Forces as Mosul Battle Rages
Rackspace Lays Off 200 Locals in Companywide Cuts
Betsy DeVos Confirmed as Education Secretary; Pence Breaks Tie
How Senators Voted on Betsy DeVos
Why Melissa McCarthy Had to Play Sean Spicer
Jeremy Corbyn may be forced to sack Diane Abbott over Brexit vote
My year of living cougarly: dating younger men turned out to be a disaster
David Beckham 'has given up hope of a knighthood in the near future'
How we are all cooking rice incorrectly and could be endangering our health
"John Kelly, Homeland Security Chief, Says Travel Ban Rolled Out Too Quickly"
Betsy DeVos Confirmed as Education Secretary With VP Pence’s Tiebreaking Vote
"Republicans vote to rebuke Elizabeth Warren, saying she impugned Sessions’s character"
"With historic tiebreaker from Pence, DeVos confirmed as education secretary"
Political Scandal Overshadows South Korea 2018 Olympic Prep
Sanders: Republicans in a panic over Obamacare - CNN Video
"Britain will be plunged into its biggest turmoil in over a century if peers attempt to thwart Brexit, William Hague warns peers as Theresa May attends House of Lords Article 50 debate in person"
SS-GB: BBC to re-examine sound after yet more mumbling complaints
Oil price recovery vulnerable as US shale confounds OPEC
Has the White House press office’s silence become a weapon in its war on the media?
CPAC rescinds Yiannopoulos invitation amid social media uproar
Milo Yiannopoulos loses his book deal with Simon & Schuster amid growing outcry
Army to allow completion of Dakota Access oil pipeline
Court questions whether US travel ban is anti-Muslim
Police pay out at least £19.5m to informants in five years
Steve Bannon Carries Battles to Another Influential Hub: The Vatican
GOP Plan to Overhaul Tax Code Gets Held Up at the Border
"Perspective | Civilities: Checking Milos Yiannopoulos’s fake facts on Bill Maher’s ‘Real Time,’ hearing the other conservative in the Christian florist case"
"Vitaly I. Churkin, Russian ambassador to the U.N., dies at 64"
Heterosexual couple lose civil partnership challenge
Liverpool killer Shaun Walmsley in armed escape
"Nascar, Once a Cultural Icon, Hits the Skids"
Ex-CIA Agent Loses Appeal Against Extradition in Kidnapping Case
Family of British IS bomber deny £1m compensation payout
Sevilla 2-1 Leicester
Woman berates McConnell at luncheon - CNN Video
South Korean court approves arrest of Samsung heir
Aslef members reject Southern rail deal
YouTube star PewDiePie rejects anti-Semitism claims
Democrats try to figure out where they're headed
State Department's silence gives others an opening
Emails reveal Pruitt's behind-the-scenes collaboration with oil and natural gas giant
Fed Minutes: Officials See Rate Increases ‘Fairly Soon’
Mexico Signals Resistance to Harder U.S. Line on Immigration
ABB Takes $100 Million Charge After ‘Criminal Scheme’ at South Korea Unit
Bernie Sanders Loyalists Are Taking Over the Democratic Party One County Office at a Time
Milo Yiannopoulos quits Breitbart News
Immigrant Crackdown Worries Food and Construction Industries
Most Dakota pipeline demonstrators leave protest camp ahead of deadline; a few dozens face arrest
How a scandal that started in Brazil is now roiling other Latin American countries
Former Guantanamo Bay detainee said to have turned suicide bomber
Iraq retakes Mosul airport amid cautious advances against IS
Samsung Group Heir Jay Y. Lee Is Arrested on Bribery Allegations
House G.O.P. Leaders Outline Plan to Replace Obama Health Care Act
"Tillerson, in diplomatic debut, urges Russia to pull back in eastern Ukraine"
Russia accepts passports issued by east Ukraine rebels - BBC News
Pakistan Shrine Bombing Kills Scores in Worst Attack in Months
Samsung chief Lee arrested in corruption investigation
"On eve of confirmation vote, judge orders EPA nominee to release thousands of emails"
Samsung boss arrested in South Korea’s explosive corruption scandal
USA Gymnastics: Larry Nassar faces trial for abuse claims
Islamic State suicide bombing at Pakistan shrine kills 75
Britons injured in Norway boat accident
Harward Said to Turn Down Post of National Security Adviser
Samsung Scion Follows Father's Path in Scandal Not Just Business
How Canada Curbed Foreign Workers and Hobbled Its Meat Industry
Uber’s Former Chief Adviser Fined for Illegally Lobbying Chicago Mayor
How to Win a Trade War With China
Harward says no to national security adviser role
"Flynn changed story to FBI, no charges expected"
Man jailed over rape of teenage girl at university halls
Tillerson Forced to Stay at Sanitarium in German Village for G-20
House Intelligence Committee open to probing Michael Flynn
Pentagon Chief Rules Out US-Russia Military Collaboration
Samsung chief Lee arrested as S.Korean corruption probe deepens
What Are Your Rights if Border Agents Want to Search Your Phone?
Andrew Puzder Withdraws From Consideration as Labor Secretary
Denzel Washington interview: 'My closest friends did 50 years in prison'
Jeremy Corbyn is now less popular than Michael Foot was at the same stage of his leadership
France's Le Pen faces trial by fire as markets attack 'franc' plan
Bob Harward Turns Down National Security Adviser Job
Fund’s $600 Million Lost Week Captivates Traders
Seoul Court Approves Arrest Warrant for Samsung Heir Lee Jae-yong
"With $15 Left in the Bank, a Baby Boomer Makes Peace With Less"
Jared Kushner Delivers Critique of CNN to Time Warner Executive
Theranos Had $200 Million in Cash Left at Year-End
Flynn in FBI interview denied discussing sanctions with Russian ambassador
Washington court rules against florist in gay wedding case
"Federal immigration raids net many without criminal records, sowing fear"
AP Exclusive: DHS weighed Nat Guard for immigration roundups
Father of UK woman fighting IS praises her 'passion'
Pruitt OK'd as EPA chief over environmentalists' objections
Tony Blair calls for people to 'rise up' against Brexit
Student Debt in America Has Hit a New Record
Kraft Heinz Spurned in $143 Billion Unilever Takeover Bid
BofA Boosts CEO Moynihan’s Pay 25% as Citigroup Pares Corbat's
Conservatives Object to Obamacare Replacement's Tax Credits
US troops deploy to Bulgaria as part of NATO operation to support Eastern European allies
"My unsolicited advice for Sean Spicer, Kellyanne Conway and the team"
Five things Pruitt can do to cripple the EPA
Unilever Rejects $143 Billion Offer From Kraft Heinz
Tony Blair's new mission: To change U.K. minds on Brexit
"Car bomb in Turkish town kills 3-year-old, wounds 15 people"
Tillerson staying at sanitarium during G20 meeting: report
Ukraine rebels accuse OSCE of aiding Kiev forces
Factcheck: Tony Blair's imperfect Brexit claims
Business rates: Lord Tebbit leads new rebellion as three former trade secretaries demand reform over rising taxes
UK to be hotter than Mediterranean next week
Here’s why markets are fearful of a Marine Le Pen victory
Scott Pruitt Confirmed as EPA Chief by the Senate
Energy Companies Face Crude Reality: Better to Leave It in the Ground
Immigrant ‘Dreamer’ Case May Be Heard Next Week
"Scott Pruitt, longtime adversary of EPA, confirmed to lead the agency"
Betsy DeVos being guarded by U.S. Marshals Service
Southern California rain eases; north facing renewed storm
"McCorvey, who was at center of Roe v. Wade, dead at 69"
"Pence says US to hold Russia accountable, stand with NATO"
Blind cleric jailed for 1990s terror plots dies in US prison
Roe v Wade: Woman in US abortion legal test case dies
Dutch populist Geert Wilders talks of Moroccan 'scum'
Michael Watson 'carjacking': Ex-boxer and friend injured
"About 1,800 'vulnerable' day-old chicks dumped in field"
"Russia Watches U.S. Reassure Allies, and It's Disappointed"
Lavrov on U.S. Election Hacking Claims: ‘Give Us Some Facts’
Poland Hails Pence's Russia Stance and Seeks More U.S. Troops
"Superbugs, Climate Chaos Have Bill Gates and the UN Worried"
France's Le Pen Denies Allegations Her Aides Had Fake EU Jobs
SpaceX Halts Rocket Launch 10 Seconds Before Planned Liftoff
Boris Johnson Was Called Out for Equating Brexit With ‘Liberation’
Tillerson presides over abrupt shakeup at State Department
"Omar Abdel-Rahman, 1993 World Trade Center bombing orchestrator, dies"
"Norma McCorvey, Roe v. Wade figure, dies"
SpaceX aborts flight due to rocket issues
More rain in store after 3 killed in California storms
"Geert Wilders, a Dutch Nationalist Politician, Calls Moroccan Immigrants ‘Scum’"
Republican Health Proposal Would Redirect Money From Poor to Rich
"Mexico City, Parched and Sinking, Faces a Water Crisis"
Pence Backs NATO; Russian Official Touts a New World Order
Family of Suspect in Kim Jong Nam Killing Says She Shot Prank Videos
California’s Dams Set to Face New Stress Tests
SpaceX Postpones Capsule Launch Seconds Before Liftoff
Analysis | Why John McCain’s #resistance is bad for Democrats
"Norma McCorvey, Plaintiff in Roe v. Wade, Dies at 69"
Kraft’s $143 Billion Bid for Unilever Highlights Squeeze in Consumer Goods
US vice president visits former Nazi concentration camp
Pence and Merkel embrace NATO but differ on transatlantic partnership
"Simply stated, Neil Gorsuch is steadfast and surprising"
"Norma McCorvey, Jane Roe of Roe v. Wade decision legalizing abortion nationwide, dies at 69"
DeVos criticized teachers at D.C. school she visited — and they are not having it
Draft DHS guidelines seek to aggressively detain immigrants
Iraqi forces launch offensive to drive IS from western Mosul
SpaceX launches rocket from NASA's historic moon pad
Kraft Heinz withdraws $143B bid to buy Unilever
Kraft Heinz drops Unilever takeover bid
War Is the Climate Risk That Europe's Leaders Are Talking About
Even Some Erdogan Diehards Flinch at Giving Him More Powers
Dealmakers Battle for Chance to Run World's Biggest Chemical Company
Russiagate: What kind of scandal?
Russia Will Accept Passports Issued by East Ukraine Separatists
"New, more powerful storm takes aim at California"
Mosul assault: Iraq troops make headway against IS - BBC News
"Norma McCorvey, ‘Roe’ in Roe v. Wade, Is Dead at 69"
A Young Reporter Makes a Soft Query and Pleases an Upset President
"Len Deighton: A wrong turn, Hotel Berlin and how I wrote SS-GB"
How the wife of former Sky Sports presenter Richard Keys 'realised he was having an affair'
Kraft Heinz abandons £115bn Unilever mega-deal
"SS-GB, episode 1 review: Dystopian Nazi nightmare is more timely than ever"
Senior Tory urges Philip Hammond to protect businesses from 'looming nightmare' of rate rises
Kraft Heinz Withdraws $143 Billion Offer for Unilever
U.S. Proposal Considers Prosecuting Parents Helping Children Entering Country Illegally
"Battle for Mosul Resumes, Says Iraqi Prime Minister"
Supreme Court considers case of a shot fired in U.S. that killed a teenager in Mexico
"Firms could reduce pension generosity, ministers suggest"
Conservative group cancels speech by Yiannopoulos
"Russia's ambassador to United Nations falls ill, dies at 64"
Winter pressure 'busts NHS budget'
Iconoclast McMaster Tapped as U.S. National Security Adviser
Le Pen Gains in French Polls as Security Concerns Win Voters
A Billion Barrels of Bets Backing Stagnant Oil Price: Chart
Russia Overtakes Saudi Arabia as World's Top Crude Oil Producer
Pence: I was 'disappointed' with Flynn
What killed Kim Jong Nam? Deadly poison remains a mystery
First on CNN: Senator seeks answers on border cell phone searches
Milo Yiannopoulos' controversial book is canceled
"2 Police Officers Shot, 1 Fatally, After Responding to Car Crash in Whittier; Suspect Injured: LASD"
Uber is not the only tech company that mishandles sexual harassment claims
"Vitaly Churkin, Russia’s U.N. Ambassador, Dies at 64"
The Downfall of Kellyanne Conway
Jean-Claude Juncker: UK faces hefty Brexit bill
Europe wants Britain to pay billions into EU schemes up until 2023
From Atticus to Zilpha: what the cast of Taboo look like out of character
Vice President Mike Pence Vows U.S. Support for European Union
"Vitaly Churkin, Russia’s Ambassador to the United Nations, Dies Suddenly"
"Samsung Heir, Seeking to Remake Family Legacy, Instead Faces Scandal"
Smartphone Addicts Behind the Wheel Drive Car Insurance Rates Higher
Wall Street Starts to Contemplate GE After Jeff Immelt
Kim Jong Nam Killing Caught on Video
"With Their Elevated Homicide Rates, Four Cities Stand Out"
AP FACT CHECK: Were hands of Obama-era border agents tied?
Supreme Court seems split in case of boy's death near border
"Milo Yiannopoulos apologizes for remarks, quits Breitbart"
British suicide bomber dies in attack on Iraqi forces in Mosul
"Wells Fargo Fires Managers, Denies Bonuses in Account Probe"
Mexico and Canada Say Nafta Should Be Re-Negotiated With All Three Nations Seated At The Table
A nation of immigrants enters dark chapter
"Spicer: At some point, laws are laws - CNN Video"
Pruitt tries to soothe worries at EPA
Israeli soldier gets 18 months for fatal shooting of Palestinian attacker
Ben Taub gets 'all clear' after SWAT search finds no evidence of shooting
Italian authorities investigating possible smuggler funding of migrant rescue boats
"Melbourne plane crash: CEO, lawyer, ex-FBI agent among Americans killed"
"Marine Le Pen refuses headscarf, nixes talks with Lebanese cleric"
British man who launched Isil suicide attack was Guantanamo Bay detainee awarded £1m compensation
Britain told there will be no 'caveats or concessions' from French after Brexit - just an unbreakable 'Franco-German position' under Emmanuel Macron
Milo Yiannopoulos Resigns From Breitbart News
Vladimir Putin told to keep out of Stoke by election after pro-Russia Twitter accounts target Ukip and Paul Nuttall
Breitbart’s Milo Yiannopoulos resigns following outrage over his past comments about pedophilia
Pruitt to EPA employees: ‘We don’t have to choose’ between jobs and the environment
Claudio Ranieri: Leicester City sack Premier League-winning manager
Most oil pipeline opponents leave North Dakota protest camp
"Immigrants change up their routines, brace for arrest"
Republicans who won after rowdy town halls now avoiding them
Mass slaughter in Brazil prison exposes gang war over drugs
Police release audio of suspect in Indiana girls' deaths
Storm Doris: Woman killed as UK hit by winds reaching 94mph
Terminally ill Bradley Lowery 'has new tumour'
Owners told not to use dangerous tumble dryers after all
Exxon Caves to Oil Crash With Historic Global Reserves Cut
Now Even the Fed's Worried That Stock Volatility Is Too Low
Spirit Air's CEO Says Rivals' Super Cheap Seats Could Backfire
Rep. Jason Chaffetz: People at my town hall 'intended to bully and intimidate' me
LIVE: Sen. Tom Cotton town hall
"Constituent to senator: 2020, you're done! - CNN Video"
US troops wounded on the front lines in Mosul
Fed Officials Not Losing Patience Fast Enough to Hike in March
David Bowie is dead – so why did he beat every living artist at the Brits?
Mexico slams US immigration plan as Tillerson arrives
Kim Jong-nam’s Killing: A Geopolitical Whodunit
"Pence, Missouri governor join cleanup at vandalized Jewish cemetery"
Milo Yiannopoulos’s Pedophilia Comments Cost Him CPAC Role and Book Deal
"Andy Warhol’s Death: Not So Simple, After All"
The 17 British Guantanamo detainees and the £20m compensation fund: Where are they now?
Cloudflare Reverse Proxies Are Dumping Uninitialized Memory
Britain's curry houses disappearing because owners 'aren't innovative enough'
Thousands of emails detail EPA head’s close ties to fossil fuel industry
Analysis | Reince Priebus is having a very good week
"Away from Iraq’s front lines, the Islamic State is creeping back in"
Former House speaker predicts 'Obamacare' won't be repealed
"Net migration to UK falls by 49,000"
White House expects Justice crackdown on legalized marijuana
Bills targeting transgender bathroom access are floundering
U.S. Gas 'Pain Train' May Chug Along as Spring Fever Grips Bears
"Who, exactly, is running US foreign policy?"
Girl seriously injured in sports hall ceiling collapse
Saudi Arabia $2 Trillion Aramco Vision Runs Into Market Reality
Justice Department Reverses Obama Private Prison Order
White House briefing bar: Media groups condemn exclusion
"Bannon, Pence send contradictory messages to EU"
Senators want Russia-related materials preserved
Analysis | Making America great again apparently includes Cold War-era nuclear dominance
DOJ walks back guidance discouraging use of private prisons
White House Indicates Potential Crackdown on Recreational Marijuana
Most scientists 'can't replicate studies by their peers' - BBC News
Alphabet's Waymo Alleges Uber Stole Self-Driving Secrets
"Bill Maher, Faulted for Booking Milo Yiannopoulos, Takes Credit for His Fall"
The Pruitt Emails: E.P.A. Chief Was Arm in Arm With Industry
Storm Doris: Travel chaos as commuters warned not to travel from several major stations as 'weather bomb' batters Britain
Claudio Ranieri sacked as Leicester City manager nine months after winning Premier League title
Guantanamo Bay detainee Jamal Al-Harith's links to Isil recruiter raise fears that taxpayers funded Manchester terror cell
Alt-right leader expelled from CPAC after organizer denounces ‘left-wing fascist group’
The NCAA’s Madness Over March
Kellyanne Conway: Feminism associated with being ‘anti-male’ and ‘pro-abortion’
Ted Cruz predicts second Supreme Court vacancy this year — but doesn’t explain why
Federal agents ask domestic flight passengers to show IDs in search for undocumented immigrant
Law professors file misconduct complaint against Kellyanne Conway
Government Clears Dakota Access Pipeline Protest Site
Dakota Access oil pipeline camp cleared of protesters
"Troubles inquiry into British soldiers is 'unfair', minister says as he calls for 'inappropriate' system to be overhauled"
"Ban on Recreational Marijuana to Be Enforced, White House Says"
Mexico foreign minister vents 'irritation' at Rex Tillerson
Tottenham 2 KAA Gent 2: Dele Alli red card puts Spurs on their knees and out of Europe
John Lewis cuts hundreds of jobs amid online shift
Plane evacuated after landing gear collapses
Storm Doris to bring snow and winds of up to 80mph
France opens full fake jobs inquiry into candidate Fillon
AP Exclusive: DHS report disputes threat from banned nations
White House defends contacts with FBI over Russia reports
White House bars major news outlets from informal briefing
Witnesses: Bar gunman shouted 'get out of my country'
Bill Cosby won't face a barrage of accusers at his trial
Olathe shooting: India shocked after national killed in US
Violence against women bill dedicated to rape victim
Blind man Tasered as cane mistaken for gun in Levenshulme
Marijuana Industry Angered by White House Reversal
French Prosecutors Extend Investigation Into Fillon
"White House blocks CNN, other news organizations from press briefing"
White House correspondant descibes block - CNN Video
Tapper: White House excluding the press is 'un-American'
White House effort to justify travel ban causes growing concern for some intel officials
White House denies wrongdoing in conversations with FBI
"States' rights for bathrooms, but not for marijuana"
Boehner: Obamacare repeal and replace 'not what's going to happen'
"He yelled ‘Get out of my country,’ witnesses say, and then shot 2 men from India, killing one"
"Exclusive: Leaked GOP Obamacare replacement shrinks subsidies, Medicaid expansion"
"For Kim Jong Nam, a sad ending to a lonely life"
Reality Check: Has a governing party won a by-election since 1878? - BBC News
FCC weakens net neutrality rule in a prelude to larger rollbacks
White House Bars Times and Other News Outlets From Briefing
"Inside Uber’s Aggressive, Unrestrained Workplace Culture"
Role of VX Nerve Agent in Kim Jong Nam’s Death Raises Global Alarm
Labour obliterated and a fat majority for the Tories: The results if we had a general election now
Nick Robinson on saying goodbye to his dying friend Steve Hewlett
Jeremy Corbyn knows who’s to blame: everyone but him
Reince Priebus Sought FBI’s Help in Refuting News Report on Russian Contacts
Some Media Outlets Excluded From White House Briefing
Iraq Launches Airstrikes Against Militants in Syria
Hollywood Is Left Hanging as China Reins In Investments
FCC Chairman Ajit Pai Will Seek to Suspend Privacy Rule
House GOP plans to keep some Medicaid expansion — and steer money to states that never bought in
Analysis | The big news is not the FBI leaks. It’s what’s in the leaks.
"‘I appeal to all the parents in India not to send their children’ to the U.S., distraught father says after shooting"
"Neighbor: Bar attack suspect a 'drunken mess,' not political"
Perez wins DNC chairmanship
Conditions deteriorate in west Mosul as Iraqi advances slow
Deadly insurgent attack in Homs weighs on UN-led Syria talks
Environmental Chief Promises Swift Rollback of Obama-Era Rules
"White House Denies Briefing Access to New York Times, Politico, CNN"
The Next Financial Crisis Might Be in Your Driveway
Republican lawmaker: Russia investigation needs special prosecutor
White House denies wrongdoing in FBI talks - CNN Video
Democrats: WH contact with FBI an 'outrageous breach of the FBI's independence'
Can the White House discuss open investigations with the FBI?
"Jen Psaki: Without free press, democracy dies"
"Germany: Man drives vehicle into pedestrians, shot by police"
"Malaysia says airport safe, autopsy shows nerve agent effect"
"One dead, two injured in Heidelberg car attack - BBC News"
Hate Crime Is Feared as 2 Indian Engineers Are Shot in Kansas
H.R. McMaster Breaks With Administration on Views of Islam
Dismal Voucher Results Surprise Researchers as DeVos Era Begins
"Kim Jong-nam Was Killed by VX Nerve Agent, Malaysians Say"
Terror chief Max Hill warns risk of attacks in Britain is highest since dark days of IRA
Theresa May facing double defeat over Brexit Bill as Lords debate amendments on EU citizens and final vote for MPs
Suspect in Kim Jong Nam Killing Says Oil ‘Prank’ Earned Her $90
Texas Rule on Transgender High-School Athletes Draws Criticism
Demand Lags at China’s Remote Airports
"Uncertainty over 30 hours free childcare, say councils"
Trump tweets: The media is the 'enemy of the American people'
Trump admin rescinds plan to reduce private prison use
Trump turns his fire on the FBI
Analysis: Trump paints dark picture in defense of travel ban
"The media is fact-checking Trump on terror — and, maybe, doing him a favor"
Iran’s Supreme Leader Thanks Trump for Showing America’s ‘True Face’
A Quiet Giant of Investing Weighs In on Trump
Justice Department Urges Appeals Court to Reinstate Trump’s Travel Ban
Donald Trump travel ban hearing: Have so many people ever listened live to such a dry set of legal arguments?
Court Grills Lawyers on Donald Trump’s Immigration Order
Court Hears Arguments on Trump Travel Ban: Live Analysis
How a Republican Bill Led to Countries Named in Donald Trump’s Immigration Order
Three Federal Judges to Rule on Donald Trump Travel Ban
Donald Trump’s Cabinet Is Taking Longer Than Normal to Fill
Melissa McCarthy on SNL shows the power comedians have under a Trump presidency
Trump administration to approve final permit for Dakota Access pipeline
"Melania Trump ‘has no intention’ of profiting from public position, representatives say"
Department of Defense looks to rent space in Trump Tower
Trump Travel Ban Provokes Harsh Questions by U.S. Appeals Court
Afghanistan war getting little notice from Trump White House
Trump and Staff Rethink Tactics After Stumbles
Appeals court ends hearing over Donald Trump's travel ban without announcing ruling
Federal appeals court weighs Trump immigration order
"Trump boasts approval rating, attacks media  - CNN Video"
Trump promises new immigration order as DOJ tells court to hold off
Retired admiral balks at Trump’s national security adviser offer
"R. Alexander Acosta, Law School Dean, Is Trump’s New Pick for Labor"
Here are some of the puzzling moments from Trump's first solo news conference
"NO HOLDS BARRED: Trump, in unprecedented fashion, airs grievances in an epic 77-minute press conference"
"Trump Defends Himself, Denies Links to Russia"
Trump Picks Alexander Acosta to Serve as Labor Secretary
Scott Pruitt: Controversial Trump environment nominee sworn in
Trump says he’ll issue a new executive order on immigration by next week
"Trump claims he ‘inherited a mess’ at sprawling, grievance-filled news conference"
"Analysis | Donald Trump’s combative, grievance-filled news conference, annotated"
Analysis | Donald Trump delivers a series of raw and personal attacks on the media in a news conference for the ages
"Trump, in unprecedented fashion for a president, rips press"
Trump supporters cheer his combative stance with the media
Trump seeks pause in legal fight with revised travel ban
Trump launches stinging attack on media
Donald Trump aide accuses BBC of 'fake news'
Robert Harward turns down Trump's national security adviser offer
Candidate Trump Tries to Salvage an Embattled President Trump
Trump's Second Pick for Labor Differs More in Style Than Policy
Seattle Man Faces Deportation in `Dreamer' Test Under Trump
An amazing moment in history: Donald Trump's press conference
Tapper: Trump's presser was unhinged - CNN Video
Trump asks African-American reporter to set up meeting with black lawmakers
Full transcript: President Donald Trump's news conference
Trump's performance fuels worry about his presidency
Trump voters applaud press conference
Trump called out for inaccurate information  - CNN Video
Trump promises new immigration order as DOJ holds off appeals court
Trump’s Pick to Replace Flynn Turns Down the Job
"Trump, Aggrieved and Sometimes Gregarious, Stands Up for Himself"
What Trump Is Doing Is Not O.K.
"Trump, Meeting With Netanyahu, Backs Away From Palestinian State"
"Flynn Was Brought Down by Illegal Leaks to News Media, Trump Says"
‘Unbelievable Turmoil’: Trump’s First Month Leaves Washington Reeling
"Trump Voters Show President They Can Complain on Twitter, Too"
"Russia Deploys Missile, Violating Treaty and Challenging Trump"
Donald Trump insists presidency is 'fine tuned machine' after extraordinary 75-minute press conference in which he attacks press
Trump raises spectre of 'nuclear holocaust' amid questioning over Russia
Donald Trump's  decision to fight chaos with chaos is a winning strategy for now - distracting from his troubles with Russia
Trump Lets Loose Against Critics
"Trump Administration Plans New Immigration Order Next Week, Ends Legal Push in Appeals Court"
Trump Administration Backs Away From Russian Reset
"Trump’s pick to replace Michael Flynn as national security adviser turns down offer, people familiar with decision say"
"In an erratic performance, President Trump shows his supporters who’s boss"
"Analysis | If Trump can’t arrange his own meeting with the Congressional Black Caucus, how does he unite the country?"
Analysis | ‘They friends of yours?’: Trump asks black reporter to set up meeting with Black Caucus
AP's National Guard Story Is A Lesson About How News Works In The Trump Era
Analysis | Fact-checking President Trump’s news conference
The rise of Trump has led to an unexpected twist in Germany’s election: A resurgent left
"Trump leaps back into campaign mode, raps media anew"
Cities ask federal judge to keep Trump travel ban on hold
"Trump, With Praise for Boeing CEO, Hints at Big Fighter-Jet Deal"
"Trump's In-Laws May Put Fannie Mae, Freddie Mac in Tough Spot"
Is Russia's obsession with Trump waning?
Pushkov: Trump and advisers differ on Russia
Is Russia's honeymoon with Trump over? - CNN Video
Donald Trump: How US President sees the world
Trump and jobs: A running fact check
There's one thing going right for Trump: The economy
HUD official fired for criticizing Trump
"Trump, Battered in Washington, Is Buoyed at Boeing Rally"
"‘I Inherited a Mess,’ Trump Says, Defending His Performance"
White House Plans to Have Trump Ally Review Intelligence Agencies
Sweden to Trump: What happened last night?
"In 77 Chaotic Minutes, Trump Defends ‘Fine-Tuned Machine’"
Trump Campaign Aides Had Repeated Contacts With Russian Intelligence
"Trump Calls Press ‘Dishonest,’ Then Utters Falsehoods of His Own"
Angela Merkel and European leaders resist Donald Trump ultimatum to increase defence spending or risk losing US commitment to Nato
"Donald Trump vows 'None will dare challenge US military might', White House denies 100,000 National Guard to deport illegal immigrants"
"At Boeing, Trump returns to an economic message after a week of controversy"
"Trump Team’s Growth Forecasts Far Rosier Than Those of CBO, Private Economists"
"Trump Says Keith Kellogg, Three Others ‘In Play’ for National Security Adviser Post"
"German defense chief hits Trump attitudes on torture, Russia and Muslims"
Analysis | John McCain just systematically dismantled Donald Trump’s entire worldview
Analysis | President Trump’s approval rating is at Barack Obama’s all-time low
Trump family’s elaborate lifestyle is a ‘logistical nightmare’ — at taxpayer expense
Analysis | Here’s why Trump’s attacks on ‘fake news’ succeed
Trump calls the media ‘the enemy of the American People’
Trump's plan for spike in defense spending faces big hurdles
"Trump rallies supporters, tears into 'dishonest media'"
"Kelly: Trump is working on a ""streamlined"" travel ban"
Donald Trump savages media at Florida rally
China grants Trump a trademark he's been seeking for a decade
"First Sons Donald Jr., Eric Preside at Trump Dubai Golf Opening"
Trump brings supporter on stage during rally - CNN Video
Why Trump wants you to hate the media
Trump bashes media at Florida campaign rally
Trump takes feud with press to campaign rally in Florida
Full Transcript and Video: Trump News Conference
Trump Chooses H.R. McMaster as National Security Adviser
Why the White House Is Leakier Than Trump Tower
Yellen Can't Halt Trump Gold Rally That Hedge Funds Bet Against
Is It Time to Call Trump Mentally Ill?
President Trump Rally in Florida
Donald Trump’s Revised Travel Ban Would Cover Seven Countries From Prior Order
"Trump attempts a reset with a rally, new staff and a renewed fight with the media"
DHS Secretary: Trump administration considering ‘more streamlined’ version of travel ban
Trump plans to talk Sunday with at least four possible national security adviser replacements
Perspective | Will Pence’s loyalty to Trump be returned in full by the president?
"Trump steps up security aide search, focuses on health care"
Europeans wonder if Trump will act on Pence's reassurances
Trump says remark about Sweden referred to something on TV
"As Trump makes foreign moves, Tillerson avoids the spotlight"
Trump Says Remark About Sweden Referred to Something on TV
Trump interviews candidates to fill national security slot
Priebus denies collusion between Trump campaign and Russian officials
Kasich: World leaders 'just not sure' where Trump stands
Trump's Sweden comment raises questions
Trump supporter: I salute a cardboard Trump - CNN Video
Carl Bernstein: Trump's attacks on the press 'more treacherous' than Nixon's
Limbaugh on the news media: 'They're enemies of Trump'
"Trump, an Outsider Demanding Loyalty, Struggles to Fill Top Posts"
Trump State Visit Debate Gives U.K. Lawmakers Time to Sound Off
Former Trump pal Russell Simmons leads 'I Am A Muslim Too' rally against president
"Trump Has a 'Very Big Personality,' Says Australia's Turnbull"
A Jewish Reporter Got to Ask Trump a Question. It Didn’t Go Well.
What a Failed Trump Administration Looks Like
Popular Domestic Programs Face Ax Under First Trump Budget
"Donald Trump's defence minister distances himself from the president's war on the media, and Republicans praise a free press"
Trump Administration Considers Change in Calculating U.S. Trade Deficit
A Friend and Former Business Partner Speaks Out Against Donald Trump
"In Marshall, Va., Support for Donald Trump Hasn’t Wavered"
"Shadow president or mere shadow? In Europe, Pence seeks to reassure allies unnerved by Trump."
Trump called the press ‘the enemy.’ Reince Priebus says he meant it.
Fox News anchor Chris Wallace warns viewers: Trump crossed the line in latest attack on media
Perspective | Could reporters be hunted down if Trump goes after leakers?
Analysis | Fact-checking President Trump’s rally in Florida
Donald Trump: MPs clash over UK state visit
"Sweden has no idea what Trump meant when he said, ‘You look at what’s happening … in Sweden’"
"‘We did not start this fight': In Trump era’s dawn, scientists rally in Boston"
British lawmakers to debate Trump’s state visit
Trump taps military strategist as national security adviser
"Trump tries to move past controversies, toward legislating"
Trump names Lt Gen HR McMaster as national security adviser
Trump picks Lt. Gen. H.R. McMaster as new national security adviser
Trump's aides don't want to admit the President is golfing
Pence defends Trump during Brussels trip
White House confirms adviser reassigned after disagreeing with Trump
Mattis disagrees with Trump's stance on media - CNN Video
Trump gets earful at 'Not My President's Day' rallies across America
New Trump travel ban order nearing completion
"Mike Pence, in Europe, Says Trump Supports Partnership With E.U."
‘I Am Ashamed’ vs. ‘Get Over It’: British Lawmakers Debate Trump Visit
How Can We Get Rid of Trump?
Fact Check: What Trump Got Wrong at His Rally
"Trump Pursues His Attack on Sweden, With Scant Evidence"
Trump’s ‘Winter White House’: A Peek at the Exclusive Members’ List at Mar-a-Lago
Donald Trump selects Lt General HR McMaster to fill national security adviser vacancy
McMaster Named as Trump’s National Security Adviser
"Amid Trump Controversies, Tax Overhaul’s Uncertain Path"
Trump taps Army Lt. Gen. H.R. McMaster as his new national security adviser
"Amid Russia scrutiny, Trump associates received informal Ukraine policy proposal"
Trump bobbleheads? MAGA hats? Federal workers grapple with the era of Trump.
Analysis | Trump asked people to ‘look at what’s happening … in Sweden.’ Here’s what’s happening there.
Bannon molded Breitbart into a far-right sledgehammer. How will it be wielded in the Trump era?
Millions targeted for possible deportation under Trump rules
"After Trump travel ban, immigrants seek to naturalize"
Trump denounces anti-Semitism; newly forceful condemnation
Trump comments put focus on Sweden's embrace of immigrants
Trump administration widens net for immigrant deportation
Trump Team Maps Sweeping Deportations for Undocumented Migrants
The Risks of a Trump Campaign Against Leaks
Here’s What You Missed From President Trump Today
Trump admin sets stage for mass deportations
Why Donald Trump keeps this immigrant awake at night - CNN Video
Top Trump Cabinet Officials Visit Mexico Amid Fury Over Deportation Plans
Trump keeps DACA but chips away at barriers to deportation
These Republicans didn't like Trump at first. They do now.
Melania Trump's sister shows rare behind-the-scenes look
"Split by Trump's travel ban, a family races to reunite"
Trump decries anti-Semitic acts as 'horrible' amid calls for stronger White House denunciations
From an Anchor’s Lips to Trump’s Ears to Sweden’s Disbelief
"A Back-Channel Plan for Ukraine and Russia, Courtesy of Trump Associates"
‘Last Night in Sweden’? Trump’s Remark Baffles a Nation
Are Liberals Helping Trump?
Senior Donald Trump aide warns European Union it can expect 'hostility' after Brexit
"Trump Administration Tightens Deportation, Detention Rules"
"Trump Denounces Anti-Semitism After Criticism by Jewish Groups, Others"
"Donald Trump Would Reconsider Bannon’s Role on National Security Council If Asked, White House Says"
"Trump administration issues new immigration enforcement policies, says goal is not ‘mass deportations’"
"Trump’s new national security adviser: A soldier who can say ‘No, sir’"
Trump decries anti-Semitic acts as ‘horrible’ amid calls for stronger White House denunciations
100 days of Trump claims
Trump administration poised to change transgender student bathroom guidelines
Riots erupt in Sweden’s capital just days after Trump comments
Analysis | The Trump presidency exists in a bubble
Trump administration to lift transgender bathroom guidance
Trump Said to Delay Revamped Immigration Order Until Next Week
Air Force Stumped by Trump's Claim of $1 Billion Savings on Jet
Poll: Trump's approval rating continues to dip
Trump administration poised to rescind guidelines on protections for transgender students
Trump's disapproval rating keeps creeping up
Contradicting Trump on Russia: Russian Officials
Ivanka Trump Calls for Tolerance After Threats on Jewish Centers
GOP senator says she’s open to demanding Trump’s tax returns as part of Russia probe
"At a town hall in Trump country, an America that’s pleading to be heard"
Trio of military men gain growing influence with Trump
US factory CEOs to Trump: Jobs exist; skills don't
Is Donald Trump a conservative? We asked CPAC
Opinion | Donald Trump has given the Mexican president the biggest gift he could wish for
"CPAC leader blasts 'alt-right,' as conservatives define agenda under Trump"
"Some Teachers, Principals And Students Condemn Trump Transgender Policy"
Trump on deportations: 'It's a military operation'
Trump requests intel report to justify travel ban - CNN Video
Lawmaker: Trump lawyer discussed Ukraine deal
"Colbert Rides a Trump Wave, While Fallon Treads Water"
New Trump Deportation Rules Allow Far More Expulsions
Trump Strategist Steve Bannon: ‘Every Day Is Going to Be a Fight’
U.S. Official’s Diplomatic Line in Mexico Differs From Trump’s
Schools Assess Bathroom Policies After Trump Rescinds Obama Order
Trump’s withdrawal of guidance on transgender student rights leaves bathroom questions up to schools and states
"Trump touts recent immigration raids, calls them a ‘military operation’"
Republicans distance themselves from Trump’s agenda at rowdy town halls
Bannon: Trump administration is in unending battle for ‘deconstruction of the administrative state’
Tech Companies Are Speaking Out Against Trump's Transgender Ruling
"LISTEN: States, DOJ Argue Whether Trump's Travel Ban Should Stay Suspended"
Katy Perry takes dig at Donald Trump and Theresa May in politically charged Brits performance
Trump Is Poised to Remove Protections on Transgender Students’ Rights
"Trump blasts media, anonymous sources _ after WH uses them"
"Trump promises border wall 'soon, way ahead of schedule'"
GOP Senators Embrace Awkward Russia Probe That Could Hurt Trump
Trump Administration Makes Its First Move to Build Border Wall
NASA Studying Manned Trip Around the Moon After Prod From Trump
Trump is costing the US friends
Trump White House Bars News Organizations From Press Briefing
"Former border patrol officials question Trump's plan to add 5,000 border agents"
Trump Rescinds Rules on Bathrooms for Transgender Students
I Ignored Trump News for a Week. Here’s What I Learned.
"Donald Trump bars New York Times, CNN, Los Angeles Times and Politico from White House press briefing"
Nigel Farage barnstorms US conservative jamboree and predicts Donald Trump and Brexit-inspired 'global revolution'
Trump Says His Victory Marked Win for Conservative Values
"Donald Trump to Call for Repeal of Obama-Era Water Regulation, Carbon-Emission Cuts"
Trump tells conservative gathering that his supporters are the GOP’s future
Analysis | Fact-checking President Trump’s CPAC speech
Analysis | Donald Trump hasn’t changed. Conservatives have. And CPAC just proved it.
Analysis | Donald Trump’s CPAC speech proves it: He’s totally obsessed with the media
‘None of these big quagmire deals’: Trump spells out historic shift in approach to trade
"White House blocks CNN, New York Times from press briefing hours after Trump slams media"
DHS report casts doubt on need for Trump travel ban
"In Trump's first speech to Congress, will decorum hold?"
Trump Says He Won't Attend White House Correspondents Dinner
Trump Seeks Credit for America's Debt Reduction
FBI refused White House request to knock down recent Trump-Russia stories
Trump declines to attend White House correspondents' dinner
Trump's call for US nuclear supremacy raises questions
Trump lashes out at media for failing to report debt decrease
Trump trashed Paris in his CPAC speech. The city’s mayor fired back.
Sanders burns Trump with taunting tweet about the size of his inauguration crowd
Trump Intensifies His Attacks on Journalists and Condemns F.B.I. ‘Leakers’
"Weakened Democrats Bow to Voters, Opting for Total War on Trump"
Trump’s Blistering Speech at CPAC Follows Bannon’s Blueprint
Fact Check: Trump Blasts ‘Fake News’ and Repeats Inaccurate Claims at CPAC
Donald Trump Takes On Familiar Targets—Intelligence Agencies and the Press
Reagan and Trump and the swift transformation of the GOP
Top Republican says special prosecutor should investigate Russian meddling in Trump’s election
"Trump administration sought to enlist intelligence officials, key lawmakers to counter Russia stories"
A Trump voter’s message to retailers: ‘Keep your mouths shut about our president’
Trump will not attend the White House correspondents’ dinner
Analysis | Trump is upset the media is not reporting a meaningless statistic about the national debt
Analysis | The remarkable inconsistency of Trump’s attacks on the media
Trump’s taunts are stirring a level of nationalism Mexico hasn’t seen in years
Briton David Ezekiel presumed murdered in South Africa
Woman guilty of 'horrific' Sheffield murder
Christine and Roger Solik found murdered in South Africa
Helen Bailey murder: Fiance Ian Stewart found guilty
AP FACT CHECK: Trump botches murder rate
Trump makes false statement about U.S. murder rate to sheriffs’ group
Killing in Malaysia Seen as Evidence of North Korea’s Illegal Acts
Who killed North Korean leader Kim Jong Un's half-brother?
Life of Slain North Korean Fueled Notion He Could Return to Rule
Malaysia arrests North Korean man in connection with death of Kim Jong Un’s half brother
"China suspends North Korean coal imports, striking at regime’s financial lifeline"
Battle for Mosul: Iraqi forces take key village near airport from ISIS
More North Korean Suspects Sought Over Kim Jong Nam Killing
Emerging Details Point to North Korean Plot in Scion’s Killing
Exclusive: Malaysia asks for China's help in identifying Kim Jong-nam's body as tensions with North Korea rise
What One Photo Tells Us About North Korea’s Nuclear Program
"Planned Back-Channel Talks Between U.S., North Korea Scuttled"
Malaysia murder mystery breaks with North Korean assassin tradition
Malaysian forensics test samples in N. Korea killing
N. Korea: We'll reject Malaysia autopsy of Kim half brother
"N. Korean envoy blasts Malaysians, calls for joint probe"
"Biological terrorism could kill more people than nuclear attacks, Bill Gates to warn world leaders"
Bill Gates: Bioterrorism could kill more than nuclear war — but no one is ready to deal with it
McMaster: It's OK to want to beat terrorists - CNN Video
Did UK Guantanamo payouts go to Isil? Government under pressure to prove some of £20m compensation did not fund terrorism
Pakistan army launches first nationwide anti-terrorism operation
‘My daughter’s death will not be used’: Parents furious over Trump’s false terrorism claims
Trump's terrorism claim is baloney
ISIS Bombing of Pakistani Shrine Kills At Least 75
Attacks near Syria town captured from ISIS kill 60
Can McMaster steer Trump clear of ISIS disaster?
Use of weaponized drones by ISIS spurs terrorism fears
Men sentenced for having sex with mentally disabled adults
"Alabama grandma found guilty of murder for making girl, 9, run until she died"
Baby died after nurse fed her day's worth of food in an hour
Teen says he blackmailed his mom into having sex with him
"Draven Rodriguez, teen who posed with his cat in front of lasers for yearbook, commits suicide at age 17."
"Girl, 14, charged after video posted on social media shows toddler performing sex act on her"
"Two girls died looking for a toilet. This should make us angry, not embarrassed"
"More than 2,000 families in Manila, Philippines lost their homes to a fire (caused by a firecracker) during New Year's Eve. What a welcome to 2016"
"Pastor's daughter, 16, falls more than 100ft to her death from giant swing thrill ride at Christian summer camp"
Father Details Daughter's Heroin Addiction In Obituary
Dad pleads guilty to letting daughter's teeth severely rot
"Father of boy, 4, who shot and killed 6-year-old friend sentenced to prison"
Eight-Months-Pregnant Teen Murdered And Boyfriend Decapitated By Craigslist Sex Buddy
Congress Is About to Take Food Away From the Poorest People in America
Gorilla expert’s throat slit in hit ordered by chef she had sacked
"Man Goes To Dentist To Get 3 Teeth Pulled, Dentist Pulls 32"
The horrible reason one woman had to wait 77 years for her PhD
Teen killed after startled friend fires shot through bedroom window
Man told friends an hour before he died that his father was doing heroin and stealing money; father stabs him to death claiming he was in a cult.
Virginia teen admits to killing parents for taking his iPod
Wrongful death lawsuit by family of woman who died waiting for ambulance thrown out because she did not make 911 call herself
Arizona Woman Nearly Dies as Brain Fluid Leaks Out Her Nose
"Dad, 83, with dementia dies after locking himself out of council care home"
"Man shoots intruder dead, finds out it's his own 15-yo son"
Man who says he escaped Auschwitz makes stunning admission
Pimp found holding baby in Akron-area hotel room while prostitute had sex with client
N.J. woman who just finished jail term for 3rd DWI convicted of 4th
First grader humiliated by school for being 1 minute late
Woman killed boyfriend by stabbing him 25 times in face with stiletto heel
What if you were created in order to be abused?
Drunk man who beat zoo monkey to death now faces up to 7 years in Idaho prison
Lesbian brutally beaten by girlfriend's brother at Thanksgiving dinner cause he disapproved of relationship.
"Mum, 18, charged with baby oven torture"
The Sixth Mass Extinction May Actually Be Here
Texas Homecoming Queen Dies on her way Home from Prom
100-year-old axes sleeping wife in alleged murder-suicide
Eleven-Year-Old Ohio Girl Charged With Murder in Death of 2-Month-Old Baby
Home sweet homewreck: This is the worst reno story you will ever hear
4chan user posts pictures of dead woman in Port Orchard
"Newborn abandoned in dumpster had flies all over her, couple who saved her now fight for adoption"
Law Student Sent To Jail For False Rape Allegations
"She killed the teenaged cyclist while driving her SUV, now she's suing his grief-stricken family"
Virginia girl found eating herself in cage in mobile home; parents Brian and Shannon Gore charged
Dad dies of rabies after trying to treat son’s dog bite by sucking blood from wound
Body of woman ‘dead for a year’ only discovered when bank inquired about a debt
Police Officer Gang-Raped Escorting Dead Sister in India
Teenager mauled by lion she was kissing
Cellphone photo of alleged Bronx killer holding his mother’s severed head is released
Syrian refugees not welcome in 31 U.S. states
Family pens frank obituary after daughter's heroin overdose
Gravestone of Hillary Clinton's father vandalized in Pa. cemetery
Woman who died after high-speed chase had open liquor bottle in car (photos)
Landlord accused of setting married couple on fire in Miss.
"Father accused of fatally stabbing 22-year-old son, blaming cult"
"Couple waits years for help, discovers attorney is disbarred"
It’s only getting worse to die in America
North Miami Beach man 'cooked alive' while using sauna
Elderly man died trying to give CPR to wife
"Girl, 11, dies on amusement park ride, mutilated beyond recognition"
"Toddler died from 'asphyxia by drowning'; mom pleads not guilty, smiles throughout hearing"
'Selfie' led to couple's cliff deaths in Portugal?
Woman killed by boyfriend was known as little princess
"Boys, 15 and 10, charged with raping a baby"
'You should all be ashamed of yourselves': Sister of dead 9/11 responder slams museum officials for hosting cocktail party - NY Daily News
Police in tears as two young sisters' bodies found
NSA member charged with beating his 3-year-old son to death only months after being adopted from Korea - NY Daily News
"Girl, 11, raped after surviving heart surgery"
Infant with rabies infected father and brother by biting them
Disturbing Pics: Father of 18 month-old boy dies as he slips into a drain while taking shelter from rain
Missing Wisconsin toddler died of excessive heat; keys found with body in locked car trunk
"Death of Idaho boy, 6, ruled suicide"
Pony dies in sex attack
French woman caught in custody battle with Saudi prince falls to her death
"Natasha Smith, Journalist In Egypt, Details Horrifying Sexual Assault In Cairo's Tahrir Square"
Aleppo mourns one of its last paediatricians killed in air strike
Chess player accused of cheating with hidden camera and Morse code messages
"Man forces way into home, beats woman, stabs her 16 times, and rapes her. Man still at large."
"Mother accused of whipping, pepper spraying, child she handcuffed to a dumbbell"
Landscaper who killed ducklings with lawnmower sentenced to jail
Teacher at Pa. school rocked by sex scandals allegedly singled out female victim in front of class
Pa. mom facing prison in infant's death blames two-year-old daughter for crime
Vietnamese-American kills man in bar for staring at him
Lacey Spears Found Guilty Of Killing Her Child With Salt
Toddler found by grandparents after staying with the bodies of his parents for 4 days after murder-suicide
"Up to 35 inmates dead, 20 comatose, after apparent mass suicide in Venezuelan prison"
"Tennessee man killed in icy crash called his mom, ‘I’m going to be fine’"
Deputy apparently commits suicide after partner charged with ripping off drug dealers
Devastated Mom Mourns Twin Daughters Killed While Trick-Or-Treating
Schoolboy jumped to his death after completing final GCSE exam
Hiker found in RMNP died by suicide
"Boy, 14, found dead after shooting himself in a bathroom stall at middle school"
Loyal dog starves but refuses to leave boy's grave for a fortnight
Girl falls to her death while hiking with parents at Yellowstone National Park
Girl who died of cancer left secret messages for her family on mirror back
Seven people die trying to get 75 cents from well in Cambodia
"Two men raped sisters, aged 5 and 7, for 3 days"
Torture over delivering girl child drives woman to suicide in Palghar
Graphic cow abuse video released as Idaho advances 'ag-gag' bill
Missouri man charged for killing toddler stepdaughter over cake - KansasCity.com
Paralyzed deer hunter chooses to end life support; dies
French girl's secret sex abuse film snares father
"Baby dies after \""highly intoxicated\"" mother passes out on her - baltimoresun.com"
Toddler died in consultation room after hour-long wait to see nurse
Father of missing beauty queen found hanged
Pemberville puppy shot and killed in front children
Man arrested for driving wife to suicide over having a daughter
Girl's dead body sexually assaulted in Pakistan
A lesbian woman has been brutally raped with a toilet brush and murdered in what is believed to have been a hate crime in Ekurhuleni
Charges dropped against EMT who merely called 911 as pregnant woman died
Boy allegedly murdered by friend for 12 cents
Man Set On Fire By Homeless Man Outside 7-Eleven Has Died
"Rehtaeh Parsons suicide: Mother says teenager was raped, bullied"
Mother died hours after being told baby would be stillborn
Sexual abuse victim killed herself after giving evidence at choirmaster trial
Police investigating death of Caylee Anthony missed vital Google search
Family died in agony after eating mushrooms
19 killed as elevator plunges 30 floors in China
Murdered teen tweeted about being stalked
Brownsburg Police identify 4 teenage victims from deadly Morgan County crash
"Pa. girl, 2, found dead in woods"
Former airman gets 10 to 25 years for infant son’s murder
"Naked Mom, Drugs In Toys, Starving Kids"
Approved death claims related to GM ignition switch recall rise to 84
Boulder DA says no murder charges to be filed in case where baby was cut from womb
"Girl sentenced to life in prison for role in murder at Akron drug, prostitution house"
Deaf immigrant jailed 6 weeks with no access to interpreter
Yellow Cab files for bankruptcy hours after $26 million verdict against company on behalf of brain damaged accident victim
"Almost 2 years after the destruction of the Zamboanga City siege in the Philippines, thousands still live in evacuation centers. More than 200 of them have died already."
$1M lottery prize goes unclaimed after winner loses ticket
Paramedic fired after taking selfies of her sticking two fingers up to patients
Bill Cosby sexually assaulted me. I didn’t tell because I didn’t want to let black America down.
Alabama home invasion suspect poured rubbing alcohol down throat of his 93-year-old grandmother
/r/feelbadnews is Rebooted! We're looking for your feedback.
"Woman murdered by ex-boyfriend petitioned for a restraining order but was denied for \""lack of evidence\"""
Parents want the world to know son who committed suicide
Woman Shot By Boyfriend’s New Year’s Celebratory Gunfire Has Died
Lodi man who 'enjoyed' torturing rabbit to death convicted of felony in plea deal
Queen of black widows murdered dozens at farm
Police believe girl murdered in disused building 'because her father helped arrest cannibal'
"Girl, 14, shot mother in face over Internet access"
‘He put his arm around her then shot her’
Woman's 50+ cats being killed after kitten gets rabies
Louisville cheerleader Dani Cogswell was found dead in football player's room
Gardener 'died after brushing past poisonous plant'
"Kentucky man gave TV interviews after allegedly murdering 3 family members, friend"
"5 year-old daughter Tia Hernlen dialed 911 when she heard her parents shot to death and murdered in Volusia County on March 28, 2005 (xpost from r/911Calls)"
South Korean safety official commits suicide after 16 die in concert accident
"Man Stabbed in the Face Inside Northeast Philly Pathmark, Unfazed Customers Continue Shopping"
Meridian woman: 19-month-old grandson 'had no skull' after abuse
Woman Killed By Falling Piece Of Gargoyle Statue Outside Church
"Man Arrested After Holding Wife As \""Slave\"" And Torturing Her (During a search of the couple's bedroom, police found a binder with the words \""Slave Manual 2014\"" on it. It contained an 11-page manual with headlines such as \""House Rules,\"" \""Punishments\"" and \""The Slave's Role.\"")"
Indianapolis man accused of baking dog to death in oven
"'I want to kill the man who raped, murdered my daughter'"
Two White police officers murder unarmed Black teen for dating their daughter (found in /r/morbidreality)
"Marine, 20, killed in car crash as he drove to surprise his eight-year-old brother on the first day of school"
Tragedy as 15-year-old sunbathing on driveway is killed by family member who didn't see her while backing out of garage
"Mom Calls Cops After Discovering Son, 15, Was Watching Porn On Living Room TV"
Parents say San Diego teen committed suicide over a viral video
She's Still Dying on Facebook
Louisville father arrested for criminal abuse; infant not expected to survive
Etawah: Girl Kills Self After Rape Bid on Sister
"Virginia dad kills two young kids, wife before turning gun on self in Father’s Day massacre"
911 call in ‘Slenderman’ stabbing released
Girl Uses Mutilated Cat To Show Her Inner Feelings (NSFL photo)
"Child Clings To Life After Brutal Sexual Assault \""The whole left side of his head is gone.\"""
Missing wife of decapitated Georgia man found dead
Pregnant woman died weeks after UK surgeon 'removed ovary instead of appendix'
Woman accused of starving son to death: 13-year-old weighed 21 pounds when he died
"Daughter, 13, allegedly lured mom into garage so boy, 15, could cut her throat: Should they be charged as adults? | PennLive.com"
"Caught cheating in exam, Indian student commits suicide in Dubai"
Pakistani man chops off girl's nose for refusing to marry him
Young mother beheaded in front of her two-year-old son after becoming trapped in the doors of a Russian elevator
Sister whispered final message to lift tragedy boy (3)
"Dad drops son from high-rise, jumps to death"
"CCTV shows girl, six, being led away before she is raped and murdered in Thailand horror"
Tragic case of girl aged 3 found sobbing next to body of devoted East Hull mother Sammy Morley
Sally Ann Okuly Killed By Car On Her First Walk After Motorcycle Crash
"Ultra-Orthodox Sex Abuse Whistleblower Describes \""Child-Rape Assembly Line\"""
Witness 'too scared' to call police after seeing violence against two year old girl at Watanobbi
Mother of 3 dies in freak accident in front of young children
"Slawson said he had sex with her after she died, but “only for a short time because she was dead and it just wasn't right\"""
"'Dad, Dad it’s not working': Tragic last words of asthmatic boy as his father battled to save him"
Sister Shot Sister Over Facebook
Father killed on walk to honor bullied son who committed suicide
Man murdered after suspects respond to Craigslist ad
Tortured woman hacks alcoholic husband to death
"Soiled diapers, dogs, listeria found at daycare where two-year-old died"
Minor girl commits suicide after being molested
Coroner: Student bled to death in dorm room after delivering baby
Found in dead hoarder's house: skeleton of wife he reported missing in 1985
Report: San Diego surfer committed suicide
Boy (11) commits suicide after being 'scolded for not studying hard'
"Good Samaritan Saves Drowning Girl, Dies Weeks Later"
"13 year old boy charged over 'wrestling' death of sister, 5"
"Woman, 31, died in hospital after bungling NHS staff thought she was faking a coma"
"Man, 41, dies after falling into a meat blender at an Oregon processing plant"
Toddler killed by dog in south Fulton County
"Woman mutilated man's body after killing him, deputies say"
Third member of family in suicide pact dies
"Woman Killed, Child Raped in NY Mall Carjacking"
Michigan woman who killed grandson struggles with key questions from jury at murder trial
Russian woman murdered husband over cat
Lovers' leap: Photographer captures moment suicide couple jump off 40 metre high bridge
Anorexia sufferer died after being discharged early due to NHS cuts
Father tells how boat propeller killed son
Stafford Hospital scandal: the victims who died needlessly
'Monster' husband laughs as wife describes torture
"Girl, 15, ‘raped, impregnated’ by own father, files charges"
Sydney tourist jailed for false rape claim
"Human, animal remains found in Slidell home; suspect sought | Local News"
58 Years Ago Today - Our Lady of the Angels School Fire - 92 Children Killed 3 Nuns
Parents plead guilty to neglect after police find dead bug in disabled son's breathing tube
Psychotherapist accused of sexually assaulting court-referred patient
Boy who gave toy gun to Tamir Rice: 'It feels as if I'm the one to blame'
"L.I. teacher choked, punched and kicked by irate mom: cops"
"Teen lived with dead girl, 3, in home; police search for parents, other kids"
Prosecutor accused of misconduct in disputed Texas execution case
Brazil bus crash: More than 50 dead after vehicle plunges off cliff on one of world's deadliest roads.
"Baby’s throat cut with power saw, grandmother in custody"
14-year-old boy tried to have family killed
A 16-year old minor abducted and murdered allegedly by city officials --- revisiting a grim story from the Philippines I covered as a news reporter last November
"Woman who stole, euthanized neighbor’s dog receives 3-6 month, prison sentence"
"Rafida Ahmed, wife of Bangladeshi American writer Avijit Roy, stands next to his body after he was hacked to death in Dhaka, Bangladesh, 26 Feb. 2015. She was also wounded in the attack. [NSFW]"
Hurricane Sandy Victims Say Damage Reports Were Altered by Insurance Companies to Cheat them out of Insurance Coverage
"Man Murders His Wife, 2 Children, Her Boyfriend and Himself…"
Father faces murder charges after 2-month-old son struck with coffee mug during argument with baby's mother
"A Michigan woman accused of murdering her newborn was pregnant when she was arrested last year, and last month gave birth to a boy — who is now missing"
'He said my head is bursting. I went up to get a cold pack and when I came back he was unconscious' - farmers share stories of tragic loss
Teenage girl punched to the floor and raped during horrific attack in Salford
Massachusetts man killed wife in argument over Christmas gift
"Man brutally murders 10-year-old daughter for \""committing adultery\"""
US officers shoot Canadian man on border bridge
Claims that boys were murdered by VIP sex ring are credible and true - Scotland Yard
"12-year-old Folsom boy killed himself -- bullied for being a cheerleader, taken out of school"
Dying girl asks 'Why are your crying daddy?'after doctors fail to spot illness
Tragedy of rider who ‘took own life’ after loss of her beloved horse
Man given life for killing mother
"Man allegedly murdered, dismembered, buried his wife then claimed she left the state"
Men died after 'worm infected kidney transplants'
Man died after being stabbed 11 times by brother
Polish woman had threesome with disabled husband's killers
Rotherham police 'ripped up files'
Employee killed by pin-setting machine in bizarre bowling alley accident
Update: Port Orchard murder suspect captured in Wilsonville
Woman found dead inside submerged car in Venetian Bay
Ex-SDPD lab tech suspected of girl’s murder commits suicide
"Nevada school knew 13-year-old was being bullied before suicide, didn't tell girl's parents"
"Man, woman found dead in Brooklyn apartment after ingesting cyanide in suicide pact"
"Deaf woman heartbroken after deaf dog shot, killed"
Man jailed for killing wife and son
"The wake of chef who killed, cooked trans wife"
Baby died in crib while parents drank for 16 hours
Disturbing case of cat abuse caught on tape being investigated
Baby girl killed in dog attack
Akron school bus driver killed while saving 10-year-old girl
"Oklahoma Highway Patrol trooper arrested, accused of rape"
Stalker raped pregnant woman then forced her to breastfeed him
Pictures show aspiring model scarred by dentist drill
Meth-addicted husband and wife whose newborn died 12 hours after birth seek release from jail
Scarborough man shot on street while carrying baby
"Tragic details of 11-year-old’s death shock neighbors, police"
Father of dead Boston boy commits suicide in front of police
Man arrested in child abuse case: Father allegedly boarded up home with kids inside
Corrections officer says he killed his mother
Woman mauled in pit bull attack; 'The screams were horrific'
"Widow: Husband died on Southwest Airlines flight 'A defibrillator was on board and could have been a lifesaver if used quickly, but Caroline Jordan claims a flight attendant said his chest was too hairy to use it.'"
"9 year old girl accidentally shoots her instructor in the head, he dies"
Texas police chief shot dead as he tried to arrest driver who was wanted for graffiti
'She died trying to save me': Man on torment of losing girlfriend
Heartbroken girlfriend killed herself after partner died while they travelled the world
Girl (9) died from fall after begging her dad for spin on hay trailer
"Child murder suspect wanted to die and \""take somebody with him\"""
Gang who killed British medical students in Borneo 'high on Crystal Meth'
How could parents go 24 hours before calling 911 about missing 6-year-old?
Priest gets three years jail for abusing young girls
"After Brutal Home Invasion, Some Scars Never Heal"
Woman’s mutilated body with stab marks on private parts found at Lucknow school
Dad found with penis chopped off: Police no longer seek suspects
"Mom who killed self, daughters with nitrogen gas was despondent over sons suicide"
A SWAT team blew a hole in my 2-year-old son (UPDATE)
Jealous husband shot wife because she 'left him'
"Fear grips Prince Albert following horrific assault of Marlene Bird (\""Half her face was off\"")"
"Father, daughter killed because woman stopped car to help ducks"
A mother-of-four died after doctors misdiagnosed her cervical cancer 30 times
Teen dies hours after high school graduation in botched shopping trolley game
Decomposed human leg found in Ohio home's closet
"Tragic student put cyanide in his drink, inquest told"
Rabbi &amp; pals stole $12M from school for disabled kids: DA
Florence woman indicted on more than 100 federal charges of producing child pornography; husband indicted on 51 counts | AL.com
Forth Bridge suicide victim was ‘sextortion’ target
Blind-drunk cop shot stranger 6 times
Man killed crying son so he could play video games
Hospital let 22-week preemie die despite mother’s urgent pleas
Nut allergy teenager's last words were “I’m not going to make it” as her siblings watched her die
Actress's newborn son dies in father's arms as he slept on sofa
Gang-raped 12-year-old dies in hospital
"Child Struck, Killed By Vehicle Hours After Father's Funeral"
Louisiana man arrested after getting caught on camera brutally beating his dog
"Tributes flood in for tragic Kyle Darker, 12, found hanged at his home"
Qian Liu’s ex-boyfriend describes watching on webcam her struggle with intruder night before she was found dead
Horrific photos of pet dog locked in kitchen and left to die by Bristol solicitor
"Washington dad locked up after suffocating 2-year-old, attempting suicide"
3 teens held in shed torture of 16-year-old
Fruitland Park house where young girl died in septic tank had code violations
"DA: Sex, Torture Case is ‘Horrific, Unimaginable’"
"New report shows horrific pictures of 11,000 executions in Syria"
"Girl, 14, fatally stabs half-sister, 11, 40 times in suburban Chicago slaying because she felt unappreciated: Cops - NY Daily News"
Woman who lured man to 'inhuman' torture by offering sex is spared jail
Dad describes son’s suicide
Tonsillectomy leaves 13-year-old girl brain dead.
"Calgary police have now charged a woman in the death of her 7-year-old son, who they allege died after she tried to treat his strep infection with holistic remedies"
Child found handcuffed to porch with dead chicken around his neck | CharlotteObserver.com
Cleveland and Lisa Cox return adopted son to Ohio children's services after raising him for 9 years
"Boy, 3, Murdered After He Wet The Bed"
Trick-or-treater hit by minivan in SW Houston dies - Houston Chronicle
"Barberton police say couple drugged, photographed sex acts with 4-year-old girl - Break News - Ohio"
Beverly Hills rabbi busted for ‘molesting boys in Brooklyn’ | New York Post
3 Children Die in Bronx Fire
"Man's body found hanging in Paris flat, eight years after he died"
Painful end to musical duo: Husband's suicide comes hours after wife's death
Northern Ireland firm admits blame over horrific feed mixer death
Window blind caused my daughter's death within seconds
Boy shot in the face in Chicago now even more afraid of the dark
"Man got girls drunk, then handcuffed and abused them"
"Tacoma woman's suicide letter blames ex-husband, his sister"
Teen who filmed girl's sexual abuse jailed
Woman gets life sentence in torture of fiance’s daughter
Briton jailed for net plot to kidnap child to eat
Hong Kong couple jailed for torturing maid who was forced to wear diaper
"End for mother Allyson McConnell, who killed her two sons"
Swiss murder suspect caught in Poland after 4-day manhunt
Pittsburgh Zoo blames mother for her 2-year-old son's mauling death
Phoenix baby sitter accused of child abuse
Children ‘exposed to sexual abuse’ at mental hospital; ministry reacts
Detectives find necrophiliac's video
Teenager’s text boast of stabbing rival 12 times
Pilot 'abused position to molest African orphans'
Colorado teen dies after being shot by close family friend in 'prank that went bad'
Teenager commits suicide on her birthday
Woburn High student witnessed the stabbing death of his friend’s mom over video chat
18-Year-Old in Coma After Breast Augmentation Needs Tracheotomy
Cops: Man Brutally Murdered Childhood Friend Over Theft Of Playstation 3
Boy Dies After Eating Groundhog Infected With Bubonic Plague
"Man beat and murdered 2yo after argument with toddler's mother, court told"
Grandmother died from malnutrition and left looking like 'a skeleton' while under nursing home care
Stray dogs found eating abandoned newborn girl's body
'Hide plant food from children' warns coroner after toddler dies
"In letter, Louisiana teen details torture, abuse and murder of parents"
"‘Had to get rid of her,’ teen who is accused of trying to kill 7-year-old says"
"Husband abducts, tortures, abuses and slashes ex-wife with blade for nine days"
Cruel bully tells wife to lie still 'like wood' as he kicks her in brutal Moss Side beating when she ran out of flour
Woman accused of brutal killing 'had drank four bottles of vodka'
"I thought she wasn't mine so I killed her, man murders 4-year-old daughter"
Dead woman found in Chester apartment had been strangled; son faces murder charges
Girl murdered by maid gets tearful sendoff
Death of impaled teen described as 'pure accident'
Houston police: Burned baby died from mom's homemade salve
Search for person who left five mutilated puppies in a dumpster while still alive
Woman died trying to save son in deep well
"After 39 yrs of shifting bodies, Shamaiya Dasi calls it a day"
Fears mother of baby found in sewage pipe in China could attempt suicide
"Daughter killed, mother sacked"
"Man kills sister, commits suicide"
Afghan woman recounts how US soldier killed her husband in rampage; case set for court-martial
"OKC man mutilated face of 10-week-old puppy, police say"
Trio who beat homeless man to death jailed
Teenage boy died on the operating table after surgeon 'tore a vein with the wrong instrument'
"Week-old baby died after being bitten by jack russell, inquest hears"
"Pot House Slayings: Three Dead, Baby Found Alive, Up To 70 Pit Bulls"
"5-month-old boy shot, killed in American Fork"
Lafayette girl called father 19 times before carbon-monoxide deaths
Mother lay dead under rubbish for 19 months and no one noticed
"Body of dead newborn is discovered, brought home by family dog in Oklahoma City "
"Officials: Texas woman killed husband, kids, self"
Woman accused of having three-way sex on top of dead men
10 killed in China train-bus collision at start of annual travel rush
Massachusetts police find blood-stained pillow in dead baby's crib
The day I saw 248 girls suffering genital mutilation
Man Who Killed Octopus For 'Art Project' Angers Divers
Tortured 'skeleton dog' rescued from the brink of death
"Boy murdered grandparents for insult to mom, police say"
Man defending his transgender girlfriend slashed by 350-pound man at Greenwich Village McDonald’s
Another Trans Woman Murdered and Mutilated in Brazil
Family grieving after ‘miracle baby’ who nearly died at birth shoots himself with father’s gun
Police: Florida teen killed 2-year-old brother
"Despite baby dying after getting herpes, Orthodox rabbis say they’ll defy city Health Department law on archaic circumcision ritual, metzitzah b’peh, in which rabbi draws blood from penis with his mouth"
British engineer killed himself in Morocco days after wife died in fall
"Bishop admits to mutilating girl, 9"
Double tragedy: Aurora shooting victim learns her daughter was killed
Afghans cheer execution of innocent woman caught in love triangle between two Taliban rivals
Tortured and raped after family fails to pay her dowry
O.C. man gets 65 years in sexual assault of 7-year-old girl
Mother 'chatted online' as son died
"N.J. woman seeks $150,000+ from 13-year-old for Little League accident"
Doctors remove girl's teeth by mistake
Police tell murdered bride's husband: 'You'll find another wife'
'My father is a triple murderer': Teenager's startling admission during live chat show interview about eloping with her boyfriend
A 21-year-old college student accused of killing a housemate told police he ate the victim's heart and part of his brain after he died.
x/post from Morbid Reality Pedophile raped baby until she bled and got a slap on the wrist more info in comments
"Girl sexually assaulted by three people, prosecutor says"